

Contacts

Malendeihalyna@gmail.com

+380686775388

<u>Linkedin</u>

<u>GitHub</u>

<u>Telegram</u>

Tech Skills

- HTML
- CSS
- Saas
- Responsive/Adaptive design
- GIT
- JavaScript
- React
- REST API
- Tailwind

Soft Skills

- · Attention to details
- Brainstorming
- Research
- Analysis
- Perseverance

Languages

- English | Pre-Intermediate
- Ukrainian | Native
- Polish | Fluent
- Russian | Fluent

HALYNA TULCHII

Junior Fullstack Developer

Summary

Junior front-end developer with experience in designing, developing and supporting web platforms. Equipped with a diverse and promising skill set. Knowledge of various languages, built-in development tools and experience with HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, responsive design, Git and others, which you can see in my skills column on my resume. Able to effectively manage himself during independent projects, as well as collaborate as part of a productive team.

Projects

Filmoteka Link [HTML5, Parcel, SCSS, JS]

Filmoteka - everything about movies of film industry. Team Learning Project. Application for searching and storage movies. Display popular movies with using themoviedb.org API.

Role: Developer

<u>IceCream Link</u> [HTML5, Parcel, SCSS, JS]

Icecream company website with responsive layout, burger menu, modal window and attractive design.

Role: Developer

WebStudio Link [HTML5, Parcel, SCSS, JS]

A website with a responsive layout.

Role: Developer

Portfolio [HTML5, SCSS, React, Tailwind]

AMy personal portfolio, website with a responsive layout. Role: Developer

Work Experience

PZU Centrum Operacji S.A. | Assistant March 2016 - March 2019 Poland

Key responsibilities:

- Preparation of documentation related to customer service
- Entering data into the system
- Verification of documents
- Preparation of documentation for transfer to the archives

Armatis-LC Polska | Consultant December 2015 - February 2016 Poland

- Consultant of permanent client
- Contact with current customers to extend the contract
- Presenting the current offer during a telephone conversation
- · Advising clients on choosing the best offer, product or service

Education

IT School GolT (Kyiv)

Student | Fullstack Developer September 2022 - July 2023 | Ukraine

Vistula University Vistula Group of Universities (Warsaw)

Master | Finance and Accounting October 2016 - June 2018 | Poland